const questions = [
    Question1 = {
        Question: 'This is Question1',
        Answer1: 'This is Answer1',
        Answer2: 'This is Answer2',
        Answer3: 'This is Answer3',
        Correct: '2',
    },
    Question2 = {
        Question: 'This is Question2',
        Answer1: 'This is Answer1',
        Answer2: 'This is Answer2',
        Answer3: 'This is Answer3',
        Correct: '1',
    },
    Question3 = {
        Question: 'This is Question3',
        Answer1: 'This is Answer1',
        Answer2: 'This is Answer2',
        Answer3: 'This is Answer3',
        Correct: '0',
    },
    Question4 = {
        Question: 'This is Question4',
        Answer1: 'This is Answer1',
        Answer2: 'This is Answer2',
        Answer3: 'This is Answer3',
        Correct: '1',
    },
    Question5 = {
        Question: 'This is Question5',
        Answer1: 'This is Answer1',
        Answer2: 'This is Answer2',
        Answer3: 'This is Answer3',
        Correct: '0',
    },
    Question6 = {
        Question: 'This is Question6',
        Answer1: 'This is Answer1',
        Answer2: 'This is Answer2',
        Answer3: 'This is Answer3',
        Correct: '1',
    },
    Question7 = {
        Question: 'This is Question7',
        Answer1: 'This is Answer1',
        Answer2: 'This is Answer2',
        Answer3: 'This is Answer3',
        Correct: '2',
    },
    Question8 = {
        Question: 'This is Question8',
        Answer1: 'This is Answer1',
        Answer2: 'This is Answer2',
        Answer3: 'This is Answer3',
        Correct: '1',
    },
    Question9 = {
        Question: 'This is Question9',
        Answer1: 'This is Answer1',
        Answer2: 'This is Answer2',
        Answer3: 'This is Answer3',
        Correct: '0',
    },
    Question10 = {
        Question: 'This is Question10',
        Answer1: 'This is Answer1',
        Answer2: 'This is Answer2',
        Answer3: 'This is Answer3',
        Correct: '0',
    },
]